Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world overflows with color
Truth and lies confuse our eyes
Use your heart to truly see
The truth lies just ahead
Hey you could do better
Truth and lies
Can't escape this soul's gray haze
Bring along all your courage
And maybe you can save the world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mr. K surrendered?
This way
I failed you, sir
He got away by jumping into the river
But he's already injured
He can't have gone far
Actually, Dottie
Dorothy
You don't need to blame yourself
A revealed sin
Is far better than a disguised virtue
Shaker
Here.
You have three days
to find Mr. K, who stole the Doctrine fragment.
Do not fail.
Understood.
Dorothy.
Here.
Immediately begin collecting the Eternal Flame.
There must be no mistakes this time.
Don't let me down again.
I swear on my honor and charm.
This time, I won't disappoint you.
Please save me, Miss Jingjing.
What did you just say?
I know your heart is as pure and kind as an angel's.
So please, you have to save me.
You say I'm pure and kind?
Yes, yes, and gentle and cute.
Gentle and cute?
Locky has never said that about me.
Of course cute, of course.
I'm telling the truth.
So please, you have to save me.
Then how do you want me to save you?
Ever since I failed my last mission,
everyone at the Illumin-Eye treats me like dirt.
Lord Eye finally kicked me out.
So I stole the remaining copy of the Illumin Doctrine
and decided to leave the Illumin-Eye for good,
to confess all their evil deeds to the police.
But instead, I got viciously hunted down.
Oh, you poor thing.
Don't worry. Jingjing will get you to the police station safe and sound.
Really?
Give me your hand.
Wha— What is this place?
Miss Jingjing? W-Where are you?
Mr. K, off to the police station we go!
Jingjing, why are you here today?
Locky!
Today, it's just Jingjing.
I brought a poor uncle.
Where is he?
I don't see him.
Hold on.
I'll show him to you right away.
He's right here.
Come on.
Jingjing?
What are you doing?
A ghost!
Mr.K
Don't play the pity card.
What trick are you up to this time?
Confess quickly.
No, no, no.
I've already told you everything.
This time it's all the truth.
Please, you have to believe me.
See?
That's about it for the preliminary statement.
Now we move on to the details.
Sima.
Continue.
Yes.
We'll continue with the questions.
Mr.K.
Why did you leave The Illumin-Eye?
And volunteer to be a witness against them?
Hurry up and confess.
I've already said it twice!
Don't talk so sloppily. Answer now!
Okay, okay.
It's like this.
Since I failed to steal the Colitas flower,
the people in the Illumin-Eye
all mock me as a good-for-nothing.
It really stings inside.
I used to do all the grunt work.
But just because of one tiny failure,
I end up like this.
I've seen how cold the world is.
So I decided to leave the Illumin-Eye and throw in with you lot.
To show my sincerity,
I stole the Illumin-Eye's precious book,
The Illumin Doctrine,
as a gift for you all.
Well?
Ask him again.
Where is the ancient book now?
Sima.
Let's continue the questioning.
Where is that ancient book you mentioned?
Ancient book...
Where's the ancient book?
Where did the ancient book go?
Ancient book...
The ancient book
It's missing.
Missing?
Who are you trying to fool?
I think you hid it yourself.
If you still won't be honest,
don't blame us for getting rough.
This paper lists the names of all Illumin-Eye members,
and the exact location of their secret headquarters.
Since you don't believe I lost the ancient book,
then this paper is the only proof of my sincerity.
Besides, I overheard that
Dorothy is going to steal an ancient sword called the Eternal Flame from the museum.
Apparently, this ancient sword is vital
to the Illumin-Eye's ultimate plan.
I risked my life to tell you everything I know.
Whether you believe it is up to you.
Seems being a good person is really, really hard.
What do you think?
I'd believe anyone else,
but Mr.K is a master of deception.
I find it suspicious too.
Inspector Sima.
Here.
Take your men and use the list Mr.K provided.
Arrest the members of the Illumin-Eye
Jimmy, go to the service center and find the Eternal Flame
I'll take the backup squad to the Illumin-Eye base immediately
Hello?
Anyone here?
Report!
No Illumin-Eye members found in the other rooms
As expected, they got away
Secure the scene
Go notify the tech team
Keep looking for new leads
Yes, sir
Saying goodbye to today
Always feels a little lost
Look at tomorrow
Waving to me on the horizon
Each day is just sunrise and sunset
Turning through time, imagining more
In life, I look forward to
Every second, every moment
My bright eyes are gleaming
A smile greeting the sun
It weeps softly at the blinking crossroads